Audrey is a documentary, history, tv movie film directed by Helena Coan.
An unprecedented and intimate look at the life, work and enduring
legacy of British actress Audrey Hepburn (1929-1993).
Audrey Hepburn, played by Alessandra Ferri.
Audrey Hepburn, played by Francesca Hayward.
Audrey Hepburn, played by Keira Moore.
Self - Photographer, played by Michael Avedon.
Self - Filmmaker, played by Peter Bogdanovich.
Self - Biographer, played by Clémence Boulouque.
Audrey is a 2020 documentary film about the life of British
actress and humanitarian Audrey Hepburn.
Directed by Helena Coan, it was produced with the involvement of Hepburn's
elder son, Sean Hepburn Ferrer, and granddaughter, Emma Ferrer.
Originally slated for a theatrical release, it was released on DVD and Blu-ray on
December 15, 2020, as well as digitally and on Netflix on January 5, 2021.
The film has received generally favorable reviews.
The film explores themes of cinema on cinema,
famine, biography, ballet, docudrama.